- We are doing four last to leave videos,
-我们要最后四个离开视频，
and the winners of each are competing in a fifth one
每个获奖者都参加了第五次比赛
for one million dollars. (cash register chimes)
一百万美元。 （收银机铃声）
You are currently watching video number two of this series.
您目前正在观看本系列的第二视频。
So the first one was last to fall.
所以第一个是最后一个秋天。
Last to fall went for over 30 hours!
上个秋天持续了30多个小时！
A million dollars!
一百万美元！
It's a lot!
好多！
This is Nick, and his coach is Chris.
这是尼克，他的教练是克里斯。
They have matching shirts. - Yeah!
他们有相配的衬衫。 -是的！
- We gonna win it! - We gonna win!
-我们会赢的！ -我们要赢了！
- This is Omar and his coach is Jake.
-这是奥马尔，他的教练是杰克。
This is Troy and his coach is coming off a couple losses.
这是特洛伊（Troy），他的教练也因此遭受了几分损失。
- [Man] Bruh!
-[男人] Bruh！
- And this is Payton and his coach is Marcus.
-这是Payton，他的教练是Marcus。
One of their body parts must cross this line
他们的身体部位之一必须越过这条线
for it to count as a swing.
算作秋千。
If they don't, we have a ref.
如果没有，我们将提供参考。
(squealing)
（尖叫）
If they don't cross it,
如果他们不越过
they're not out,
他们没有出来，
but what'll determine if they're making an effort.
但是如何确定他们是否在努力。
- I'm very distressed.
-我很伤心。
(smooth hip-hop music)
（流畅的嘻哈音乐）
- Give you a dollar to get out.
-给你一美元出去。
You guys could split it, 50 cents.
你们可以把它分成50美分。
- Yoink!
-Yoink！
- Good thing I have another dollar.
-好东西，我又有美元。
- I'll give you two if you stay.
-如果你留下，我给你两个。
(energetic funky music)
（充满活力的时髦音乐）
- We're gonna prank our cameraman.
-我们要恶作剧摄影师。
Hit three!
打三！
(air horn)
（气喇叭）
(laughing)
（笑）
- That was scary.
-太恐怖了。
I can't hear now.
我现在听不到。
- We're doing the first challenge!
-我们正在做第一个挑战！
Stay behind that bag of chips.
留在那袋薯条后面。
Here's a marshmallow.
这是棉花糖。
If you land it in his mouth,
如果你把它放在他嘴里，
you get to push him for a minute.
你可以推他一分钟。
- [Chandler] What is that?
-[钱德勒]那是什么？
(buzzer) - Oh!
（蜂鸣器）-哦！
(groaning) - What is what?
（gro吟）-什么？
What is what?
什么是什么？
Yeah, yeah, come on!
是的，是的，加油！
- [Angry Man] Boy, if you don't get--
-[愤怒的人]男孩，如果你不明白-
(buzzer) - Wait--
（蜂鸣器）-等待-
- Wow!
- 哇！
This is where everyone else was.
这是其他所有人都在的地方。
Since you're Chandler, you can go up here.
由于您是钱德勒，所以可以上到这里。
- Ooh!
哦！
(groans)
（gro吟）
- [Jimmy] And you're not Chandler,
-[吉米]而且你不是钱德勒，
so you're back here. - What?
所以你回到这里。 - 什么？
(laughing)
（笑）
- Here you go! - All right.
- 干得好！ - 行。
- Kobe!
- 科比！
(ding) (shouting)
（叮）（喊）
Let's go!
我们走吧！
- Now that he's pushing you, is it easier?
-现在他在推你，这容易吗？
- Tons easier.
-吨容易。
- I wanna make sure I'm very clear,
-我想确保我很清楚，
you guys cannot touch the contestants
你们不能碰参赛者
or the red lights will be forced to come on.
否则红灯将被强制点亮。
- Oh, oh! - Look at this,
-哦，哦！ - 看这个，
I'm not touching him!
我没有碰他！
Ooh, look at me!
哦，看着我！
- Oh hey, look at that, Troy, Marcus,
-嘿，特洛伊，马库斯，
can't touch him.
不能碰他
- [Uneasy Man] No, no, no--
-[不安的男人]不，不，不-
- Did he get you?
-他抓到你了吗？
Did he get you?
他得到你了吗？
- Yeah, he got me.
-是的，他救了我。
- Troy touched Chris.
-特洛伊感动了克里斯。
Let me show you what happens
让我告诉你发生了什么
if a contestant touches one of you.
如果参赛者碰到您中的一个。
(ripping)
（翻录）
- Oh my-- - Oh my God!
-我的天哪-我的天哪！
- [Chris] There is no way!
-[克里斯]没办法！
- See how Nick is suffering?
-看看尼克的痛苦吗？
This is why you guys shouldn't touch them.
这就是为什么你们不应该触摸它们的原因。
I don't know if you're out there,
我不知道你是否在那里
if they swing and just touch you with their toenail.
如果他们摆动并且用脚趾甲触摸您。
- Like that?
- 像那样？
- But did you?
-但是你呢？
- Yes!
-是的！
- Jake just got touched!
-杰克感动了！
Hey, I won't move yours as far.
嘿，我不会把你的移到最远。
We'll put his right here.
我们将他放在这里。
And I think it's time to move his back.
而且我认为是时候退缩了。
There we go, now he's back to normal.
我们去了，现在他恢复了正常。
- Troy, we don't wanna just pick on you, so--
-特洛伊，我们不想只接您，所以-
(air horn)
（气喇叭）
♪ Oh my God ♪
哦，天哪！
(laughing)
（笑）
- Yo! (claps)
-哟！ （拍手）
(smooth hip-hop music)
（流畅的嘻哈音乐）
- You can't go too deep, I'm telling you now, bro,
-你不能太深入，我现在告诉你，兄弟，
it's going on two days.
这要持续两天。
- [Cameraman] You know you're saying that
-[摄影师]你知道你是在说
you have to win now.
你现在必须赢。
- No one's gonna last more than a day after, like--
-没有人会持续超过一天，就像-
- [Cameraman] Interesting.
-[摄影师]有趣。
- I'm gonna win in a day.
-我要一天赢。
- You have to run through them without getting touched.
-您必须不被触碰而穿过它们。
We're gonna use the smoke to make it harder for them to see.
我们将使用烟雾使他们更难看见。
Hut, hut, hike, go!
小屋，小屋，远足，走！
(aggressive rock music)
（激进的摇滚音乐）
- [Blunt Man] Nope!
-[Blunt Man]不！
(shouting) - Was it?
（大喊）-是吗？
Jake, you got touched!
杰克，你感动了！
- Yeah, Frankie! (growling)
-是的，弗兰基！ （咆哮）
- Hut, hut, hike!
-小屋，小屋，远足！
Give him more!
给他更多！
Give him--
给他 -
He got him!
他抓到他了！
Chandler, are you ready?
钱德勒，你准备好了吗？
- Hey, no!
-嘿，不！
- Hike!
-加息！
- Ow, fumble!
-噢，摸索！
(beep)
（嘟）
- To hike 2.0.
-徒步2.0。
- Ooh!
哦！
- He hurt to himself.
-他伤了自己。
So, the punishment is you have to lay
所以，惩罚是你必须躺下
under your contestant for five minutes.
在你的选手下五分钟。
- I feel like my ding dong's gonna get kicked any second.
-我觉得我的叮当会被踢一秒钟。
- Oh, this kinda nice, actually.
-哦，这真不错。
- You know what?
- 你知道吗？
- I'm a great motivator.
-我是一个伟大的动力。
- So now that you guys are all laying on the ground,
-既然你们都躺在地上，
this leads perfectly into our next segment.
这完美地进入了我们的下一个细分市场。
Chris, I need you hold this and let your guy punt it.
克里斯，我需要你拿着这个，然后让你的家伙戳一下。
- All right.
- 行。
- Distance. (thunks) (ding)
-距离。 （沉思）（叮）
- Whoa! - It's good!
-哇！ - 很好！
(ding) (shouting)
（叮）（喊）
- Shut up, I need your help, dude.
-闭嘴，老兄，我需要你的帮助。
(ding)
（叮）
- It's good!
- 很好！
(shouting) (buzzer)
（大喊）（蜂鸣器）
- Marcus, just stay under him.
-马库斯，就留在他之下。
- It's not fair.
- 这不公平。
He pushed it up closer for Chandler,
他向钱德勒推近了
but not for me!
但是不适合我！
- [Jimmy] You should just get good, have you tried that?
-[吉米]你应该变得很好，你尝试过吗？
- [Loud Man] Got him! (laughs)
-[大声男人]有他！ （笑）
(squealing)
（尖叫）
- Ad on the field,
-现场广告，
we have an ad on the field!
我们在现场有广告！
- Thank you, referee.
-谢谢裁判。
Now let me tell you about the sponsor of the video, Honey.
现在，让我告诉您有关视频的赞助商Honey的信息。
Here is how Honey works.
这是Honey的工作方式。
We're currently on Macy's,
我们目前在梅西百货，
we have a $279 mixer,
我们有一个279美元的搅拌机，
and we're gonna add it to our bag.
我们将其添加到我们的包中。
Because we have the Honey add-on,
因为我们有Honey附加组件，
all we have to do is hit apply coupon
我们要做的就是点击“应用优惠券”
when checking out on any website.
在任何网站上结帐时。
And boom, Honey actually found a coupon code
繁荣时期，霍尼实际上找到了优惠券代码
that saved us 50 bucks. (cash register chimes)
为我们节省了50美元。 （收银机铃声）
And that, in a nutshell, is how Honey works.
简而言之，这就是Honey的工作方式。
Anytime you check out on your computer,
每当您在计算机上结帐时，
it will search the entire internet,
它将搜索整个互联网，
and if it finds a coupon code,
如果找到优惠券代码，
it will apply it.
它将应用它。
Here's another example.
这是另一个例子。
Our total is $425.
我们的总额为425美元。
We hit apply coupon.
我们打了申请优惠券。
Now it's $340. (cash register chimes)
现在是340美元。 （收银机铃声）
We saved $85 by literally clicking twice
通过点击两次，我们节省了$ 85
and installing a free browser add-on.
并安装免费的浏览器插件。
Here's how you install Honey.
这是安装Honey的方法。
You hit add to Chrome, you hit add extension,
您点击添加到Chrome，点击添加扩展程序，
now you have Honey.
现在你有蜂蜜。
Even Chandler can do it!
甚至钱德勒也能做到！
- Here and here!
-在这里和这里！
- Nice! (claps)
-好！ （拍手）
And here's a list of all the websites Honey works on.
这是Honey工作的所有网站的列表。
You should really install it
你应该真的安装
'cause you'll save thousands of dollars of your live time.
因为您将节省成千上万的生活时间。
Go to JoinHoney.com/MrBeast.
转到JoinHoney.com/MrBeast。
That's JoinHoney.com/MrBeast,
那就是JoinHoney.com/MrBeast，
you'll save a lot of money.
您会节省很多钱。
And let's go back to swinging.
让我们回到摇摆。
(smooth hip-hop music)
（流畅的嘻哈音乐）
So this challenge has been goin' on for a while.
因此，这一挑战已经持续了一段时间。
- Quite some time. - Yeah.
-有点时间。 -是的
- I think it's time we bring out the Unicorn of Wealth.
-我想是时候推出财富独角兽了。
Plop the Unicorn of Wealth right here.
在这里扑通财富的独角兽。
We have some Beats, rip off of AirPods,
我们有一些节拍，从AirPods窃取，
AirPods,
AirPods，
we have an iPad,
我们有一台iPad，
a speaker,
演讲者
and an Alienware laptop
和Alienware笔记本电脑
here for the next person that gets up.
在这里为下一个起床的人。
The laptop's worth two grand.
笔记本电脑的价值为两美元。
I know you wanna get out now, go ahead and grab it.
我知道您现在想离开，继续前进。
- No, I am stayin'.
-不，我待在里面。
- [Jimmy] Okay.
-[吉米]好吧。
- Not that there. - Not that?
-不是那里。 - 不是那个？
- Not that.
- 不是那个。
- [Jimmy] Oh, not, Marcus!
-[吉米]哦，不是，马库斯！
He just said not that,
他只是不这么说
but he said something bigger.
但是他说的更大。
You might wanna have to go have a talk with him.
您可能需要和他谈谈。
You wanna be the first one out two times in a row?
您想连续两次成为第一个吗？
- It's not happening.
-没发生
- There's a lot of good stuff in there.
-里面有很多好东西。
- Oh no, not interested at all.
-哦，不，一点都不感兴趣。
- [Jimmy] Mr. Nick, I can tell.
-[吉米]尼克先生，我可以告诉。
- Guy ain't even a PC gamer.
-盖伊甚至都不是PC玩家。
He don't want that--
他不想要那个
- [Jimmy] Nick, go grab it.
-[吉米]尼克，快去抓吧。
- It's nice, but can't take it.
-很好，但是不能接受。
(smooth hip-hop music)
（流畅的嘻哈音乐）
- [Jimmy] What'd you just say?
-[吉米]你刚才说什么？
I know, Aardman, who's gonna get out first.
我知道，Aardman，谁先出去。
Is that what this is right now?
这就是现在吗？
- I'm doing a business deal, and we're gone.
-我在做生意，我们走了。
- [Jimmy] A business deal and you're gone?
-[吉米]一笔生意，你走了吗？
- A business deal and we're gone.
-商业交易，我们走了。
- [Jimmy] You, what?
-[吉米]你呢？
Now, here's my question.
现在，这是我的问题。
Are you gonna beat him to the punch and get off first?
您要击败他，先下车吗？
- I'm already on the ground.
-我已经在地面上了。
- [Jimmy] You're already-- (laughing)
-[吉米]你已经-（笑）
So you're sayin' you're ready to go.
所以你说'你准备好了。
- The way these legs hurting right now--
-这些腿现在受伤的方式-
- [Cameraman] So, Nick,
-[摄影师]尼克，
you openly said you're struggling, right?
你公开地说你在挣扎，对不对？
- I'm struggling right now.
-我现在很挣扎。
- [Jimmy] So here's the thing.
-[吉米]这就是事情。
Before I make an offer, I wanna remind you.
在报价之前，我想提醒您。
One million dollars.
一百万美元。
You could work the next 15 years of your life
您可以在未来的15年中工作
and make a million dollars.
赚一百万美元
Or you could push through and win it in a few weeks,
或者，您可以在几周内努力赢得胜利，
when we have the next challenge.
当我们面临下一个挑战时。
Having said that, $5,000 to the first person.
话虽如此，第一人称获得了5,000美元。
(record scratch)
（记录划痕）
(shouting) Oh!
（喊）哦！
Okay!
好的！
Chris, that's two challenges you lost.
克里斯，那是您失去的两个挑战。
- I gave him linguini!
-我给了他扁面条！
I couldn't have been a better coach!
我再好不过了！
- [Cameraman] You got offered $5,000.
-[摄影师]您获得了$ 5,000。
- My legs hurt so bad.
-我的腿好痛。
- [Cameraman] How do you feel now?
-[摄影师]您现在的感觉如何？
- I feel like my legs are in bad shape right now.
-我感觉我的腿现在身体状况不好。
- [Cameraman] Was it the right decision?
-[摄影师]这是正确的决定吗？
- Yes, for my legs!
-是的，我的腿！
- All right, come here, Nick, come on.
-好吧，来吧，尼克，来吧。
Come over here to the couch.
过来这里坐沙发。
Let's escort him.
让我们护送他。
Oh, hey Chandler.
哦，钱德勒。
Did you wake up from your nap?
你从午睡中醒了吗？
(grunts)
（咕gr声）
Here you go, this should ease your pain, $5,000.
在这里，您可以减轻痛苦，5,000美元。
- Cool.
太好了
- [Jimmy] You didn't win a million dollars,
-[吉米]您没有赢得一百万美元，
but you got five grand.
但是你有五个隆重的
- [Chris] How do they feel?
-[克里斯]感觉如何？
- Dude, they hurt so bad. - Do they?
-杜德，他们好疼。 -他们吗？
- The way you sit on it, it's like,
-您坐在上面的方式就像
it's like digging into right here.
就像在这里挖掘一样。
Think I have a bruise right here, actually.
认为我实际上在这里有瘀伤。
- Geez.
真是的
- [Jimmy] Payton, you already sound
-[吉米]佩顿，你已经听起来
like you're on the edge, so--
就像你在边缘，所以-
- That wasn't the business deal I was looking for,
-那不是我要找的生意，
I'd just stick up the gum.
我只是贴上口香糖。
- [Jimmy] So we already know, Payton's struggling.
-[吉米]所以我们已经知道，佩顿的挣扎。
Tony, it's really you against Omar.
托尼，对阵奥马尔的人真的是你。
Are you gonna be the one that stands up to him
你会成为支持他的人吗
and wins a million dollars?
并赢得一百万美元？
- Yes.
-是的
- [Jimmy] 'Cause if Omar wins,
-[吉米]因为如果奥马尔获胜，
that means Jake's contestant
这意味着杰克的选手
would've won the first challenge and the second.
会赢得第一个挑战，第二个挑战。
- I feel like I don't really have much pain.
-我觉得我真的没有什么痛苦。
- [Jimmy] If you win the million dollars,
-[吉米]如果您赢得一百万美元，
what would you buy with it?
你会用它买什么？
- Firstly, I'd give back to my whole family, my parents.
-首先，我会回馈整个家庭，我的父母。
$200K I'm gonna keep to spend.
我要继续花20万美元。
- Oh, only 200 grand? - Only 200.
-哦，只有200个隆重？ -只有200。
- Now we're gonna call all the contestants' parents.
-现在我们要给所有参赛者的父母打电话。
We're gonna start off with Payton's father.
我们将从佩顿的父亲开始。
- [Automated Message] I'm sorry, the person you are try--
-[自动讯息]很抱歉，您正在尝试的人-
(somber piano music)
（沉闷的钢琴音乐）
- Now we're gonna call Troy's mom.
-现在我们要打电话给特洛伊的妈妈。
Hey, are you Troy's mother?
嘿，你是特洛伊的母亲吗？
- [Troy's Mom] Yes.
-[特洛伊的妈妈]是的。
- He's been swinging on a swing for 10 hours,
-他已经摇摆了10个小时，
and if he wins, he gets to compete for a million dollars.
如果他赢了，他将争夺一百万美元。
- [Troy's Mom] Just hold on, boo.
-[特洛伊的妈妈]嘘，嘘。
Just don't think about it,
只是不用考虑
just keep swinging.
只是继续摇摆。
- Aw.
啊
- [Troy's Mom] Just go with the flow.
-[特洛伊的妈妈]顺其自然。
- How's dad doin'?
-爸爸好吗？
Is he getting any better?
他好点了吗？
- [Troy's Mom] Yes, they shocked his heart to restart it,
-[特洛伊的妈妈]是的，他们震惊了他，重新启动了它，
and then that makes him feel back to normal.
然后让他感觉恢复正常。
So, I'm gonna go and tell him what's going on.
所以，我要去告诉他发生了什么事。
Just concentrate and then don't think about, like,
只是集中精力，然后不要考虑，
oh, I'm tired, or something.
哦，我累了，还是什么。
Just don't think about it.
只是不要考虑。
- No.
-不
- [Troy's Mom] Just hang in there, baby.
-[特洛伊的妈妈]宝贝，快挂在那里。
- Oh, now I want you to win.
-哦，现在我要你赢。
Omar, get out! - No!
奥马尔，出去！ -不！
- Okay.
- 好的。
We're gonna hit the phone with the next contestant,
我们要和下一位选手打通电话，
we'll update you on how he does.
我们将向您介绍他的工作情况。
- [Troy's Mom] Okay, thank you.
-[特洛伊的妈妈]好的，谢谢。
- All right, all right, later, mom.
-好的，好的，以后，妈妈。
- [Troy's Mom] I love you, son.
-[特洛伊的妈妈]我爱你，儿子。
- All right, all right.
-好的，好的。
- [Troy's Mom] Okay, go hard.
-[特洛伊的妈妈]好，努力吧。
- Oh. - I will.
哦- 我会。
- All right, wow.
-好吧，哇。
Omar's about to call his sister.
奥马尔正要给妹妹打电话。
We're just gonna fill her in.
我们只是要填补她。
- Hey! - Hi, homey!
-嘿！ -嗨，家常！
- Hey, hey.
-嘿，嘿。
So I'm currently swinging.
所以我目前正在摇摆。
I'm doing good, slightly sore,
我做得很好，有点痛，
but I'm mostly good.
但我大部分时候都很好。
- If he wins today,
-如果他今天赢了，
he competes for a million dollars
他竞争一百万美元
in a challenge in a few weeks.
在几个星期内面临挑战。
So, if he plays his cards right,
所以，如果他打牌正确，
he could become a millionaire.
他可能成为百万富翁。
So I want you to just encourage him
所以我只想鼓励他
and give him some motivation.
给他一些动力
I'm gonna hand him back.
我要把他交还。
- Keep swinging, keep going,
-继续摆动，继续前进，
it's just, uh, however long it is.
只是，嗯，不管多久。
- [Omar] Don't worry about it.
-[Omar]不用担心。
Talk to you soon.
以后再聊。
- Call me after.
-给我打电话。
- Yes, I will.
- 好，我会的。
- Everyone just got a little bit of motivation
-每个人都有一点动力
except for Payton.
除了佩顿。
- You know what?
- 你知道吗？
We're swingin'! - Yeah!
我们在摇摆！ -是的！
- So just keep swingin'!
-那就继续吧！
- [Coach] Whoo!
-[教练]哇！
(smooth hip-hop music)
（流畅的嘻哈音乐）
- Chris, my brother, can you cart Steve onto the court?
-克里斯，我的兄弟，你能把史蒂夫推上法庭吗？
- Uh-oh.
哦
- If you get out now, you can have all the presents.
-如果您现在出去，就可以得到所有礼物。
(shouting)
（喊）
Marcus!
马库斯！
Marcus is asleep. - Sound asleep.
马库斯睡着了。 -睡着了
- Hey buddy.
- 你好朋友。
You know how we're recording these?
您知道我们如何记录这些吗？
See how do y'all rate?
看看大家如何评价？
- You did the best you could do.
-您已经尽力了。
Appreciate you comin' out here, you know what I'm sayin'?
欣赏你来到这里，你知道我在说什么吗？
- Me and Marcus had a little bit of up and downs
-我和马库斯都有点起伏
during our challenge today.
在今天的挑战中
- Yeah, we did, we did, we did.
-是的，我们做到了，我们做到了，我们做到了。
- But I think we overcame 'em when Marcus fell asleep.
-但是我认为Marcus入睡时我们克服了他们。
- I think you're right. (laughing)
- 我觉得你是对的。 （笑）
- They've been swinging for 12 hours.
-他们已经摇摆了12个小时。
- 12 hours, 12 hours!
-12小时，12小时！
(bursts)
（阵阵）
- Ooh, that was nice.
-哦，太好了。
I have a feeling you're both gonna go a while.
我觉得你们俩都要走一段时间。
Would you say so?
你会这样说吗？
I guess we'll just
我想我们只是
do a time lapse!
时间流逝！
(smooth hip-hop music)
（流畅的嘻哈音乐）
So the last to fall challenge
所以最后一个挑战
came down to Jake's contestant
归结于杰克的选手
and Chandler's.
和钱德勒的。
So this is the exact same thing.
所以这是完全一样的。
On top of that,
最重要的是，
Jake was still here at nighttime,
杰克晚上还在那里
Chandler wasn't.
钱德勒不是。
Change history, though, Troy.
但是，更改历史记录，特洛伊。
I believe.
我相信。
- I will change it.
-我会改变的。
- I don't know you guys do this.
-我不知道你们这样做。
I'm tired. (chuckles)
我累了。 （咯咯笑）
(smooth hip-hop music)
（流畅的嘻哈音乐）
It is six AM.
现在是早上六点。
I now you guys have to be tired.
我现在你们必须累了。
- I'm feeling great, Jimmy.
-我感觉很好，吉米。
- I don't get how he feels like that.
-我不明白他的感觉。
- I feel great. - At six AM in the morning.
- 我感觉好极了。 -早上六点。
- I feel great, dude, I feel great.
-我感觉很好，伙计，我感觉很好。
- You could've gone a day. - Yeah!
-你本可以走了一天。 -是的！
- Troy, you still gonna go on?
-特洛伊，你还会继续吗？
A little off, guard the table,
稍微休息一下，守好桌子，
but that's where you are,
但这就是你的位置
or are you just dragging?
还是只是在拖拉？
- I'm going off beat.
-我要跳了。
- Lemme consult the team.
-Lemme咨询团队。
I wanted to consult with the team,
我想咨询团队，
but the team's asleep.
但是团队睡着了
I might offer some money, you know,
我可能会提供一些钱，你知道，
to see who takes it.
看看谁拿走了。
Okay, let's try Chandler.
好吧，让我们尝试钱德勒。
We're offering them money
我们给他们钱
to see if anyone wants to get out.
看看是否有人想出去。
Do you wanna come talk your guy into staying?
你想和你的男人谈谈留下来吗？
He's like, asleep.
他就像，睡着了。
Okay.
好的。
So we woke up Jake, and we woke up Chandler.
所以我们叫醒了杰克，我们叫醒了钱德勒。
Now let's go offer them some money.
现在，让我们为他们提供一些钱。
(squealing)
（尖叫）
- Congratulations, you're awake.
-恭喜，你醒了。
- You know how we do things.
-你知道我们是怎么做的。
Sometimes people just need a little bit
有时候人们只需要一点
of a nudge to get out, would you agree, Chandler?
轻推一下，钱德勒，你会同意吗？
- Yes.
-是的
- For the next 30 seconds,
-在接下来的30秒内，
if someone gets out,
如果有人出去
$10,000.
$ 10,000。
- 10,000. - That's a lot of money.
-10,000 -很多钱。
- Omar, I know you want this $10,000.
-奥马尔，我知道您要这10,000美元。
- Nah, I don't.
-不，我不知道。
- What could you buy with it? (laughing)
-你可以买什么？ （笑）
- I don't want it. - No, I don't.
我不想要-不，我不知道。
- [Omar] I'm going for the million,
-[Omar]我要争取百万，
and I decided that from the start.
我从一开始就决定了
- What's going through your mind, Troy?
-你在想什么，特洛伊？
- [Troy] I wanna get that one mil, man.
-[特洛伊]我想拿一百万，伙计。
- You wanna get the million?
-你想得到百万？
But even if you win here,
但是即使你在这里赢了
you still have to win another challenge after this.
之后，您仍然必须赢得另一个挑战。
You could not win that
你赢不了
and be in the same scenario,
并处于相同的情况下
but with way less suffering.
但痛苦更少。
- [Cameraman] Yeah, Omar, you've had a smile on your face
-[摄影师]是的，奥马尔，你的脸上一直挂着微笑
this whole time.
这整个时间。
- Yeah, why not do it with a smile when you're winning?
-是的，为什么当您获胜时不笑着笑？
- [Cameraman] Would you have taken that deal now?
-[摄影师]您现在就接受这笔交易吗？
- C'mon Omar, just let me win, man.
-来吧，奥马尔，就让我赢吧，伙计。
(laughs)
（笑）
- Bruh, I'm not leaving 'til tomorrow,
-布鲁，直到明天我都不会离开，
you can stay if you want to.
如果愿意，可以留下。
Trust me when I say this, you're wasting your time,
当我这样说时，请相信我，您正在浪费时间，
I'm not leaving.
我不会离开。
- [Jimmy] The energy you have, I want that, I need that!
-[吉米]你有能量，我想要那，我需要那！
(laughing)
（笑）
- [Chandler] Are you givin' up?
-[钱德勒]你愿意吗？
- Dude, I'm breaking right now.
-杜德，我现在要打破。
- [Chandler] Do not, dude, don't break.
-[钱德勒]不要，伙计，不要打破。
- I am physically, like, hurting so bad.
-我身体很疼。
- Troy.
特洛伊
How are you feeling?
你感觉怎么样？
- I'm hurting.
我好痛
- Okay.
- 好的。
I can tell you're hurting.
我可以告诉你很痛。
So if someone gets out in the next 30 seconds,
因此，如果有人在接下来的30秒内下车，
I will give them $10,000 in cash.
我会给他们$ 10,000现金。
- I'm gonna give him one percent of my winnings
-我要给他我奖金的百分之一
if I win the million.
如果我赢了百万。
- Oh, I didn't hear that! - I told him that.
-我没听见！ -我告诉他了。
- If Omar wins, he's gonna face up against Akira
-如果Omar获胜，他将面对Akira
and the winners of the next two challenges--
以及接下来两个挑战的获胜者-
- And win off this thing. - For a million dollars.
-赢了这个东西。 -一百万美元。
You get 10 grand,
你得到十大
and you can potentially get another 10 grand.
并有可能再获得10个大奖。
- Dude, I could go for at least one more day.
-杜德，我至少可以再住一天。
(laughing)
（笑）
- Troy, all right, give him another 30 seconds.
-Troy，好的，再给他30秒。
- A million, you heard it, I need it.
-一百万，你听到了，我需要。
- [Jimmy] This is determination right there.
-[吉米]这就是决心。
- [Chandler] Keep fightin', keep fightin'.
-[钱德勒]保持战斗，保持战斗。
Omar is-- - I'm surviving.
奥马尔-我还活着。
- All right, Troy.
-好的，特洛伊。
Stick it out and go,
伸出去，
or you could walk away today with 20 grand.
否则今天您可以带着20个盛大牌走开。
I know that would help your family greatly.
我知道那会大大帮助您的家人。
So Omar has now offered two percent
因此，奥马尔现在提供了百分之二
on top of the $10,000.
在$ 10,000之上。
- And since some of you aren't that good with math,
-而且由于你们中的一些人对数学的了解不强，
if he wins a million dollars,
如果他赢得一百万美元，
two percent might not seem like a lot,
2％的比例似乎不高，
but that's still 20 grand.
但这仍然是20宏伟。
- I'm not feeling so good.
-我感觉不太好。
- If he gets up, okay, 100% up to you
-如果他起来，好吧，100％取决于你
if you wanna keep going or not.
如果您想继续走下去。
(applauding)
（鼓掌）
Omar is the winner!
奥马尔是赢家！
Let's have a draw!
让我们抽奖吧！
- You didn't--
-你没有-
- I don't even know what to say, man.
-我什至不知道该说些什么，伙计。
You killed it.
你杀了它
You got guaranteed 10 grand.
您保证10宏伟。
If Omar wins, you get another 20.
如果奥马尔获胜，您将再获得20个。
And I know that'll help for sure.
而且我知道这肯定会有所帮助。
So, I'm proud of you.
所以，我为你感到骄傲。
Everyone's proud of you.
每个人都为您感到骄傲。
Your mom, your family's gonna be proud of you for sure.
您的妈妈，您的家人一定会为您感到骄傲。
- Yeah, I feel better up here.
-是的，我在这里感觉更好。
I really wanted to win it to break, you know,
我真的很想赢它才能打破，
the losing streak. (laughs)
连败。 （笑）
- That's why?
- 这就是为什么？
That's why?
这就是为什么？
Well, I appreciate you trying for me, man,
好吧，我感谢您为我而努力，老兄，
but that was awesome.
但这太棒了。
And you're gonna get that $10,000 now.
现在，您将获得10,000美元。
- Gotta give thanks to my fans, and my family.
-要感谢我的粉丝和我的家人。
- I'mma give you that $20K, for sure, bro,
-我给你2万美元，当然，兄弟，
100%, you'll gain that $20K.
100％，您将获得2万美元。
(murmuring)
（淙淙）
- Jake, Akira won. - Yes.
-杰克，晃赢了。 -是的
- Omar won, you're two for two.
-奥马尔赢了，你是两个两。
- Two and oh.
-两个，哦。
- Which means two of the four people competing
-这意味着四个人中有两个竞争
for a million dollars will be your guys.
一百万美元将是你们。
- Honestly, one million means a lot to me.
-老实说，一百万对我来说意义非凡。
And like, my family has taken care of me all my life.
就像，我的家人一生都在照顾我。
And all I want to do is like give back to them,
我想做的就是回馈他们，
and this seems like the perfect opportunity
这似乎是绝佳的机会
through, like, getting a million.
通过，例如，获得一百万。
- Based on the comments section up in the last video,
-根据上一个视频中的评论部分，
people really like Akira.
人们真的很喜欢晃。
Well, we'll see how they respond to you, Omar.
好吧，我们将看看他们如何回应您，奥马尔。
And we'll see you in a few weeks.
我们将在几周后见。
(explosion)
（爆炸）
♪ Oh MrBeast 6000 ♪
♪哦MrBeast 6000♪
♪ Oh ♪ (Explosion)
♪哦♪（爆炸）
♪ MrBeast 600, yeah, you know his name ♪
♪MrBeast 600，是的，你知道他的名字♪
♪ He changed it once or twice ♪
♪他改变了一两次♪
♪ But I think it's here to stay ♪
♪但我认为这里就住了♪
(explosion)
（爆炸）